export default {
	"list": [
		{
			"id": 0,
			"questions": [
				{
					"id": 0,
					"question": "Breaking the Law",
					"correctAnswer": "Judas Priest",
					"answers": [
						"Metallica",
						"Iron Maiden",
						"Insomnium",
						"Judas Priest"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 1,
					"question": "Master Passion Greed",
					"correctAnswer": "Nigtwish",
					"answers": [
						"Slipknot",
						"Death",
						"Nigtwish",
						"Sepultura"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 2,
					"question": "Roots Bloody Roots",
					"correctAnswer": "Sepultura",
					"answers": [
						"Sepultura",
						"Dark Tranquility",
						"System of a Down",
						"Children of Bodom"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 3,
					"question": "The Satanist",
					"correctAnswer": "Behemoth",
					"answers": [
						"Behemoth",
						"Sepultura",
						"Metallica",
						"Death"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 4,
					"question": "I Won't See You Tonight (Part 2)",
					"correctAnswer": "Avenged Sevenfold",
					"answers": [
						"Bring Me the Horizon",
						"Immortal",
						"Gwar",
						"Avenged Sevenfold"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 5,
					"question": "All Shaw Fall",
					"correctAnswer": "Immortal",
					"answers": [
						"Nigtwish",
						"Slipknot",
						"Immortal",
						"Twisted Sister"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 6,
					"question": "Contractor",
					"correctAnswer": "Lamb of God",
					"answers": [
						"Megadeth",
						"Slipknot",
						"Lamb of God",
						"Trivium"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 7,
					"question": "We're Not Gonna Take It",
					"correctAnswer": "Twisted Sister",
					"answers": [
						"Twisted Sister",
						"Nigtwish",
						"Death",
						"Iron Maiden"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 8,
					"question": "Symphony of Destruction",
					"correctAnswer": "Megadeth",
					"answers": [
						"Megadeth",
						"Metallica",
						"AC/DC",
						"Lamb of God"
					]
				},
				{
					"id": 9,
					"question": "In the Name of God",
					"correctAnswer": "Dream Theater",
					"answers": [
						"Heaven Shall Burn",
						"Babymetal",
						"Dream Theater",
						"Born of Osiris"
					]
				}
			]
		}
	]
}